#### Contact

MIANMIANTEA2016@GMAIL.COM

www.linkedin.com/in/christy-g-b1b1295a (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

PowerPoint
Microsoft Office
Research

### Languages

English (Full Professional)

Cantonese (Native or Bilingual)

Mandarin (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Learning Excel What-If Analysis

Excel: Tracking Data Easily and Efficiently

Breakeven and Cost-Volume-Profit (CVP) Analysis

Excel 2013: Managing Multiple Worksheets and Workbooks

**Business Process Improvement** 

# **Christy Guo**

Staff Accountant II

Atlanta, Georgia

## Summary

Experienced at General Ledger, Accounts Payable, Accounts Receivable, Financial Statements, and Sales Tax. Highly effective communication and interpersonal skills; noted for being versatile, self-motivated, stable and adapting well to challenging and diverse situations. Currently enroll in GT coding bootcamp, skill:Browser Based Technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap)

# Experience

BCD Travel
Staff Accountant II
April 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Greater Atlanta Area

Greater Atlanta Area Accountant April 2014 - August 2018 (4 years 5 months) Georgia

Indiana Department of Revenue Tax Analyst July 2013 - January 2014 (7 months)

Kelley School of Business Indianapolis Graduate Student August 2011 - May 2013 (1 year 10 months) Master of Science in Accounting

Hawthorne Community Center
Tax Preparer
January 2012 - April 2013 (1 year 4 months)

## Education

Indiana University-Purdue University at Indianapolis Master's degree, Accounting · (2011 - 2013)

Guangdong University of Foreign Studies South China Business College

Bachelor's degree, International Business/Trade/Commerce · (2007 - 2011)

GT Coding Bootcamp · (2020)